OK
Hello.
This is my first time playing this song, so I think I need to check it out.
Mar-chan
Cute half-twin!
Today
I didn't see when the relationship came in
Oh, squid burrito!
We got it from Tetsuya!
Yay! It's from Tetsuya!
This is the first time... or rather, the first time in a while.
It's been a while since I've had a penlight!
Yay!
Thank you very much!
Yuu is holding it for me.
There's a paor too!
Pa-olu.
It's so cute!
Thank you very much for calling us.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much for calling us.
It looks a bit like a ticket, doesn't it?
It's a little bit like a ticket, and it shows the pattern of a journey.
The color is cute too.
There are carabiners and stickers,
There are also stickers and badges.
It's limited to the venue.
It was at the venue.
So you can only get today's badge today.
Yes, yes, yes.
Hello. Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for your hard work.
How was it?
It was a lot, but I was a little nervous,
But it was a lot of fun,
We have nine more stops to go, and eight more to go,
On the last day of the tour, we will be able to show the culmination of our power through this tour, and we will be able to show our power to the world.
Like Soshino-san.
I want to do my best so that we can show off our abilities like Soshino-san. I want to do my best so that I can demonstrate my abilities.
Let's do our best!
I would like to wait for a few months so that each one of us can grow through the tour
I will do my best to help each one of you grow through the tour.
I look forward to seeing you again.
Thank you very much.
I'm Reeju.
Is it you, Reeju?
It's over.
This is Akane Sora.
The first day of the spring tour is over.
Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work.
What do you think of this, Sora?
Thank you. We worked hard.
Is this Reju and Sora?
It's smashed.
Uru-chan, do more.
Not like that, Uru-chan.
Is this me?
Ur-chan, not like that.
Ur-chan, it's not like that.
Was it a video? Mikia, I'm not like that! Mikia, I don't mean it!
Was it a video?
It's a video.
So that's it.
The first day of the spring tour is over!
Oh no, oh no, oh no!
Hey, Koharu, don't go!
Why are you doing this?
It's going on YouTube.
Really?
I'm sorry, I'll go one more time... and that's the end of the first day of the spring tour.
Yay! So how was it?
How was it? I was very nervous because it was the first time for me to tour with a group of people, but we changed our costumes...
Shoo!
Wait, wait, wait, when is this coming out?
You're already showing the costumes.
You're showing us that you've changed. You're showing them that you've changed.
I think the costumes are nice, but how much can I say?
So, the first day of the tour in Chiba-Kashiwa is over!
How was everyone? The first day of the tour is over in Chiba-Kashiwa!
How was everyone?
It was the first ocher with the new organization.
I was so excited to see how it was going to be.
I was so excited.
And I wanted everyone to see the show as soon as possible.
I think we had a good first day.
How about you, Kobayashi?
This is my first time in Kashiwa, Chiba.
I thought it was a very nice place and I had a lot of fun.
I used the one who thought it was a nice place.
I'm sure you'll be happy to know that this is the first day of our first tour.
I'm really looking forward to the next few days.
So please look forward to the jump!
Lily Chan Championship No.1, I'm going to the other room.
Ready go!
LAST
Number three.
Ready go!
Oh no!
Mar-chan, who's always doing everyone else's work, is always doing everything.
Grandma's always doing the most
Let's talk about dinner.
I love it!
I like you.
No, no, no.
Like this...
I like it.
Today's show is in Nagoya!
It's the Nagoya show!Nagoya Show.
Today's Side Puny
Good evening.
It's over.
Who's that?
With the reddish color.
Yes, ma'am.
Sora-chan!
Too scary.
A little scary.
My voice was a little scary, too.
Sora-chan!
Hi, this is Sora-chan!
My mom and dad came to Nagoya, and my grandma came to Nagoya.
Tenju and Jeezy
Tenshu
It says "sesame" on it.
Sesame on a tree?
Oh, I see it.
That's right!
I also got some Mitarashi dango.
Dango!
You ate a big meal today.
Thank you
Delicious!
Shrimp!
It was a corner of Nagoya's specialties.
We had a corner of Nagoya's specialties. The foods we received.
Nagoya is over.
I thought it turned out better than the first show in Chiba.
This is the best part of hop-step-jumping, isn't it?
I met them where I sang today, and I am always singing, but there were always some people who were stung by the part I sang today.
I always meet them at the place where I sang today, but there are always some people who are stuck by the part I sang today, and I think, "What a cute guy!
I thought, "Who's that? I was happy that I could deliver that kind of song.
I was happy to be able to deliver such a song.
How was it?
Yeah, it was great.
It's hard to eat. It's hard to eat.
But I haven't had it for a long time.
I got it from Ruri.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, Ruri.
I have some himeki.
I'll use it.
I'm going to use it now.
Shall we go?
Mr. Yabaton's
I want to eat that cutlet.
I'd like to try it.
He bought it for me.
I'm on my way home.
I'm home...I'm home...I'm home. I'm back. I'm coming back. He is coming back.
I'm coming back.
I'm back.
Please, please.
Please.
I will sing KANOPUS.
I will sing KANOPUS. I'll sing KANOPUS - Okey-dokey. - Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee. - I'm done, I'm done, I'm done.
Today was Koko-san and hairdresser Ki!
Thank you very much.
Stage time 이 영상은 제작지원에 따른 영상입니다.me
As the show ended, everyone was getting more and more excited with their fortitude and excitement.
We had a lot of fun too. Thank you very much.
Isn't this your first time to play Canopus?
But it was the first time for me to play Canopus, so I was very nervous.
I was very nervous, but I was happy that everyone was so warm and supportive. Thank you very much.
Our next performance will be at the Fukuoka Beat Station on April 27th, so please come and join us!
Yes!
Thank you very much! Bye.u